springmetrics.com 2018-04-05

# Privacy Policy — Spring Engage

## Third Party Cookies

We may from time to time engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to the Site to help us administer the Site and improve its quality. Such third parties may use cookies to help track visitor behavior. Such cookies will not be used to associate individual Site visitors with any Personal Information. All data collected by such third parties on behalf of Spring Metrics is used only to provide us with information on Site usage and will not be shared with any other third parties.

## Information Collected From Customers

We require customers who register to use the Service to provide us with additional Personal Information as well as other information related to your organization (“Customer Information”). Customer Information includes, but is not limited to, company or organization name, address, phone number, e-mail address(es), financial qualification information such as billing name, billing address, and credit card number, as well as the number of users within the organization that will be using the Service. As part of the registration process, we may also request additional Customer Information such as your title, department name, fax number, or additional company information. Customers can opt out of providing us with this additional information by not entering it when prompted to do so during the registration process. Customers can update or remove their Customer Information at any time by logging onto the Site and editing their Customer Information within their respective account. Customers can log in to the Site and view their updated profile to confirm such edits have been accepted.

Spring Metrics uses the collected Customer Information to set up the Service for customers, which set up includes providing customers with usernames and passwords. We may also use the Customer Information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in Spring Metrics or the Service that we provide, to send information regarding Spring Metrics and its partners, to notify you about updates to the Service, or to deliver our Customer Newsletter. Customer email addresses and any Personal Information and/or Customer Information will not be distributed to or shared with any third parties. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us, or from receiving such information from us, at any time by sending an email to support@springmetics.com with the words “opt out” written in the subject line.

Except as explicitly stated at the time we request Customer Information, we will not disclose to third parties the financial or billing information provided by the customer. All financial and billing information that we collect through the Site is used solely to check the qualifications of prospective customers and to bill for the Service. Such information is not used by Spring Metrics for marketing or promotional purposes. Spring Metrics uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing. Other third parties, such as content providers, may provide content for the Site. Such content providers, however, are not permitted to collect any information about Spring Metrics customers, nor does Spring Metrics share Personal Information or Customer Information with such third parties.

Through customer’s use of the Service, Spring Metrics or its service provider will host certain data and information (“Data”). Spring Metrics will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any Data, except as expressly allowed under the Terms of Use, or as may be required by law. Individual Data records may at times be viewed or accessed by Spring Metrics only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violations of the Terms of Use, or as may be required by law. Of course, customers are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and password.

## Third-Party Sites

The Site contains links to third party websites. Spring Metrics is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any third party websites. Spring Metrics’ Site customers and visitors who link to other websites from the Site should check the privacy and security policy statements of such third party websites to understand the policies of such third party websites. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information to the owner of such third party websites. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential. Spring Metrics is not responsible for the privacy and security policies and practices of third party websites.

## Security

Our Site has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of Data under our control. When you access our Site using a browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 5.5 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that Data is safe, secure, and available only to you. Spring Metrics also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and hosts the Site in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Finally, Spring Metrics provides unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a customer logs in. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain Data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Data.

## Opt-Out Policy

Spring Metrics offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use Personal Information and Customer Information that you provide to us. If at any time after registering for information or ordering the Service you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your Personal Information and Customer Information with third parties, send a request specifying your new choice to support@springmetrics.com with the words “opt out” written in the subject line.

## Correcting & Updating Your Information

If customers need to update or change Customer Information, or organization data, they may do so by editing the user or organization record. To update a User Profile, log on to the Site and select “My Settings,” “Users” or “Company Settings” to add or update information. To update billing information please email support@springmetrics.com with the word “billing” in the subject line. To discontinue the Service and to have data returned to you, email support@springmetrics.com with the word “cancel” in the subject line. Spring Metrics will respond to your correction or update request within thirty (30) days from the date of your request.

Additional Information:

Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of this Site should be directed to Spring Metrics’ Security Administrator by e-mailing such questions to support@springmetrics.com.
